[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Shadow Punisher]
[Divine Constable Tally]
[Episode 19]
Qin Dayuan,
I know you can hear me.
Didn't you set up these 7 fish tanks
just to let me
see through the mechanism
and lure me to this place?
If so,
why are you hiding now?
If I recall correctly,
Tang Wei was unmarried, right?
Yes.
Tang Yiming died 10 years ago.
Tang Wei attained an epiphany and devoted himself to Taoism,
vowing never to marry.
If so,
check that out.
Why is there
a baby's pillow?
And why is this baby's pillow
made of stone?
The fish tanks are all in the same spot
in each room from the 1st floor
to the 7th.
The spots where the moonlight reflects on the ceilings
through the fish tanks,
from the 1st to the 7th floors,
are also almost the same.
Except for this huge deviation
on the 7th floor.
This is due to
the different height of this floor.
Each floor
of Lanyue Pavilion from the 1st to the 6th
is about 5 meters high.
But this 7th floor
is clearly much shorter.
There's only one way to explain it—
there is a hidden space
above this 7th floor.
Something's off.
This mechanism is way too obvious.
We just found out Tang Wei committed suicide,
and then you guys
found his suicide note so quickly?
Tang Wei's parents are dead.
He had no wife or children.
Then who did he
write this suicide note to?
And who does this word,
"you," refer to?
Seems like Tang Wei's suicide note
was also meant for us.
Qin Dayuan,
if you still don't show yourself,
don't blame me for being rude.
Huang Gang.
Jiang Zeshui.
Ascend to Heaven.
Is this
General Hu Hai who jumped into the furnace for liberation?
I once read the records in Tianshu Pavilion.
"Liluo has pearls, often seen in darkness;
they don't gleam like the moon, but blaze like the sun."
So it's a luminous pearl.
Throughout the records of hundreds of years,
there is only one luminous pearl
as large as this one.
It is Liluo's national treasure,
the Mirror Moon.
After Liluo fell, they searched
the entire national treasury
but failed to find this Mirror Moon.
Never thought it would be here.
Tang Yiming was an official
credited with conquering Liluo back then.
He must have
looted plenty of treasures
from the Liluo Imperial Palace.
Who exactly is this corpse?
Qin Dayuan?
Then who is
inside this 4th statue?
The corpse
inside this 4th statue
is the former Minister of Works.
He was also my master,
Tang Yiming.
Why is he here?
He went missing 3 days ago.
Why did he die here?
Butler Qin.
It must've been rough,
lurking in the darkness
on the 8th floor of Lanyue Pavilion.
But it's reasonable.
The Divine Constable Bureau is searching everywhere.
There's no way you can escape.
Well?
At this point,
are you still not going to come clean?
How should I come clean?
Why don't we
start with Kongyuzi?
Since you mentioned this name,
you must know she was my wife.
You were husband and wife after all.
Why did you have to kill her?
Because
there was one thing
you couldn't accomplish
without killing her.
Divine Constable Qingyang.
Do you want to guess...
what I
accomplished?
Huang Gang,
Jiang Zeshui,
Hu Hai, Tang Yiming—
the four of them
once joined forces to destroy Liluo.
Their deaths
are Liluo's revenge.
You got it half right.
Huang Gang and the others
caused too much bloodshed
when they destroyed Liluo,
so it was only natural
for them to feel uneasy
when they got old.
Hu Hai and the other two were long in the tooth.
Because they had
their hands coated in too much blood,
they were scared of death
and sought medical help everywhere,
but to little avail.
Therefore,
Mr. Tang told them
that he knew the way to seek immortality and liberation.
Hu Hai
was the first one.
The Young Master built
a secret passage in the sword-forging furnace.
When Hu Hai fell into the furnace for liberation,
he took Hu Hai away, killed him,
and sealed him here.
Mr. Tang couldn't use martial arts.
So of course,
the Liluo demon-men helped him
do everything you mentioned.
But Huang Gang and Jiang Zeshui
were no easy marks like Hu Hai.
So,
you renovated the Jiang Mansion and Huang Mansion,
using Lanweichun
to hide the image of Haiqu,
Liluo's God of Revenge,
in the mural.
This caused Haiqu's figure
to flicker in and out of view,
forcing the two veterans
to believe in
Tang Wei's theory of mystic cultivation.
That day,
Mr. Tang accurately foretold
the date of his own death
and jumped from this Lanyue Pavilion,
convincing Huang Gang and the others
completely.
And then,
he entrusted everything to you,
leaving you to carry out
the rest of the plan.
You guessed this part right.
In order to achieve immortality,
they all
ended up believing Tang Wei's words.
Hence,
Huang Gang climbed up the "heaven ladder,"
Jiang Zeshui crossed the lake,
and Hu Hai jumped into the sword-forging furnace.
But in the end,
they were all captured by the Liluo demon-men
and brought here.
With the Liluo people on my side,
why would I go
to so much trouble
instead of asking them to kill the guys directly?
You made Lord Huang and the others
believe that ascension was real,
only to reveal everything
at the very last moment when they were
so close to fulfilling their wishes,
and tell them
that ascension was actually a lie,
letting them die in fear.
Only in this way
could the revenge be satisfying.
The Master reached the immortal land.
The whole Huang family fell off the cliff.
Hu Hai's beloved little granddaughter
took poison.
If we hadn't arrived in time that day,
the whole Jiang family would have drowned in the lake, too.
What a cruel and ruthless scheme.
To seek revenge,
you wiped out their entire families.
Huang Gang, Jiang Zeshui, and Hu Hai.
I brought the three of them over here.
I told them ascension was a lie,
and it was their greed
that got their families killed,
leaving them crying out
in remorse
with no response.
My Lord, My Lady!
My Lord, My Lady,
Lord Yan reported that
Divine Constable Qingyang
went up Lanyue Pavilion alone!
He went to Lanyue Pavilion alone.
Could it be that
he found out something?
There is one thing that puzzles me.
Tang Wei is one of the Tangs.
Why would he take revenge for Liluo?
Master Tang had a large and rich family,
yet Tang Wei was his only child.
Could it be...
Because Tang Yiming was impotent.
Tang Wei was not Tang Yiming's child?
He was from Liluo?
Divine Constable Qingyang, you've finally got it right.
How about I tell you
a story?
Forty-seven years ago,
Great Shi attacked the capital of Liluo,
while the Moon Queen of the Kingdom of Liluo, Qiangong Linglong,
was about to give birth.
[Qiangong Linglong, Regent Moon Queen of Liluo]
Greetings, Moon Queen.
Who is the father of the child in your womb?
Please forgive me, Moon Queen.
The child is innocent.
My child
is also your child.
He will surely dedicate everything
to you, Holy Queen.
Please don't kill him.
Please allow him to sacrifice himself for Liluo.
You are very loyal to me, the Holy Queen.
In this case,
I hereby allow you
to sacrifice your life for Liluo.
I see.
Thank you for your mercy, Moon Queen.
[Huang Gang]
[Jiang Zeshui]
[Hu Hai]
[Tang Yiming]
She is in the Moon Robe.
Holy Queen, Qiangong Linglong.
We must eliminate the root!
Hold on!
The child is innocent.
Tell me!
Where is the treasure vault
of Liluo?
Tell us what you know,
and we can spare your life.
You are wrong.
Liluo's sorcery is powerful.
Only if we kill their leader
can we shatter their morale
and secure a complete victory.
Let me be frank with you.
We'll both take the treasures
and your life.
However,
if you tell us,
we can give you a quick death.
Will you tell us or not?
Guys, guys, listen to me.
Having the Moon Queen of Liluo
and the little prince as hostages,
we can make the remnants of Liluo
hesitate to attack
and yield to us.
Tang,
do not be excessively soft-hearted.
She is at death's door
and still refuses to say anything.
The so-called Liluo treasures
are probably just a rumor.
That's right.
We can kill this woman first
and then go look for the treasures.
Let's go find the treasures.
Understood!
Let's go.
Guys,
we've killed the enemy leader.
We won.
Long live His Majesty! All hail Great Shi!
-Long live His Majesty! All hail Great Shi! -Long live His Majesty! All hail Great Shi!
Tang, what are you waiting for?
His Majesty has decreed
to arrange a 3-day celebration
for us outside the city.
Save my child...
They didn't know that
after they left,
my master granted that woman's request
and saved her child before she died.
Master Tang felt sorry for them
and took the child in.
That child was Tang Wei.
Exactly.
Later,
the Liluo demon-men told Tang Wei what happened
back then.
The Young Master had long wanted revenge,
but Huang, Jiang, and the others held
high positions and great power back then.
Moreover, my master
saved the Young Master's life
and raised him,
so
the Young Master couldn't bring himself to hurt the Master.
Therefore, he kept waiting
and enduring it all
until 10 years ago.
Until 10 years ago,
he finally made a move against Master Tang?
Nope,
Master Tang died of illness.
Over the decades,
the Young Master inherited
all my master's techniques in crafting and carving.
So he faked
master's ascension to Heaven on a wooden bird
and took over Lanyue Pavilion.
Therefore,
Huang Gang and the others
firmly believed in the cultivation
to immortality Tang Wei said
only because
they witnessed Tang Yiming's ascension
to the immortal realm with their own eyes back then?
Back then, in the secret chamber of the Imperial Palace,
the Young Master's mother
died in fear.
So the Young Master
wanted them to taste
that feeling, too.
I think
Tang Wei must've
lived in agony all these years.
His death
somehow delivered him
from torment.
Nonsense.
The Young Master got his revenge
and died with a smile,
not in agony.
Divine Constable Qingyang, your life's been smooth sailing.
You could never understand this.
I understand, of course.
I just don't understand
why you only remember
Young Master Tang's feud
but ignore Master Tang's grace.
My family's land deed was seized
by Master Tang back then,
so I was forced to be sold to the Tang family
and bullied by everyone.
At that time, everyone in the Tang Mansion
looked down on me,
except for the Young Master, who treated me with respect.
So the Young Master's wish
is my wish.
I see.
I've had his revenge.
Divine Constable Qingyang,
come on!
Arrest me and bring me to justice.
Butler Qin,
since you are okay with being arrested,
why have you been hiding here?
Because I wanted
to lure the Divine Constable Bureau's personnel
to the 8th floor of Lanyue Pavilion
and tell you
what
those four people have done.
Only when the Divine Constables reveal the truth to the public...
can the Young Master and his mother
rest
in peace.
So that's how it is.
So,
you were afraid we couldn't find you
and even spread the news that
Butler Qin came to Lanyue Pavilion
to mourn for his young master 3 days ago.
I've been waiting not only for you
but also
for the people of Liluo.
Zhenzhu!
Yan,
at the Tang Mansion,
we found Qin Dayuan's body
as well as the Liluo treasures.
What?
It even involved the treasures?
If Dark Night comes to search this place,
then
the Divine Constable Bureau can easily catch them like rats in a trap
and purge Dark Night in one fell swoop.
However...
Butler Qin, how did you know
that once you disappeared,
Dark Night
would definitely come looking for you?
What do you think, My Lord?
For the Tang household to have the money to build this Lanyue Pavilion,
they must have made a killing.
Could it be...
The Liluo treasures?
There really are the Liluo treasures!
My master secretly brought back the treasures
of the Kingdom of Liluo
and hid them in the secret chamber of the Tang Mansion.
The people of Dark Night
are desperate to get the treasures
to bankroll the overthrow of Great Shi.
But they have no clue about
the whereabouts of the treasures.
After Master Tang and Mr. Tang died,
you're the only one who knows
the location of the treasures.
When you disappeared,
the Liluo demon-men
had to go find you.
I had already arranged it before I came.
The treasure is left to the Divine Constable Bureau.
Weird.
It was just reasonable for Tang Wei
to take revenge on Great Shi.
But
why would he want
to eliminate the Liluo demon-men who helped him
take revenge as well?
What do you think?
Qingyang should still be up there.
Calm down.
Meng is on his way here with the body.
How can I calm down?
I'm almost worried sick!
The Liluo imperial family
used Tang Wei's mother as a scapegoat,
so they could escape unscathed.
Therefore,
to Tang Wei and his mother,
the Liluo imperial family
were also their bitter enemies,
just like Huang Gang and the others.
Butler Qin,
there is one more thing I'd like to confirm.
Who on earth
is the former citizen of Liluo
who had been in contact with Tang Wei
over the past 3 decades?
Let me think.
Gunpowder?
My wish is fulfilled.
Once I activate the mechanism,
the entire Lanyue Pavilion will be blown away!
Wouldn't it be a pity
to destroy the Top 1 Pavilion
just like this?
Pity?
Not at all.
What a pity that the people
of Liluo didn't come.
Wait!
You can kill me,
but you cannot stop me
from igniting the gunpowder.
You've taken such great pains for this all these years.
I don't want you to end up
dying without knowing the truth.
You have waited for years.
It doesn't hurt to wait
just a bit longer, right?
Li Si!
There is gunpowder here!
No!
Don't come any closer!
No one can stop me
from reuniting with my young master.
"Young master"?
Is Tang Wei really your young master?
Or rather,
are you really Qin Dayuan?
Are you out of your mind?
He is my young master,
the one I have followed all my life.
In this case,
see who this is.
Bring it over.
Yan, go find the Chief.
Got it.
What...
What happened?
What's this all about?
Sir,
Kongyuzi, whom you killed with your own hands,
was not your wife, actually.
You...
What are you talking about?
The moon's reflection turns into the flower in the mirror,
replacing old forms with new faces.
As one of the Five Wonders of Liluo,
the Illusion of Mirrors and Water is indeed
an unparalleled disguise technique in the world.
Zhenzhu,
check the back of his head
and see if there's anything unusual.
He is really not Qin Dayuan, as expected.
I am Qin Dayuan.
I-I am Qin Dayuan.
The Illusion of Mirrors and Water
can completely alter
a person's skin, flesh,
and even bones,
making the one truly
become a different person.
Since it is sorcery,
how could it be used in Tianhuang City
under the Absolute Prohibition?
This is just a martial arts mental technique,
not sorcery.
The Illusion of Mirrors and Water
can not only change his appearance
but also his figure and voice?
What... What did I originally look like?
I want to see.
See for yourself.
Who is he? Who?
You still
haven't recalled anything?
You are the former Minister of Works,
the world's greatest craftsman,
Lord Tang Yiming.
He is Tang Yiming?
But...
But Tang Yiming is already dead,
right?
T-That's right,
Tang Yiming is already dead.
He is right in...
The Illusion of Mirrors and Water combined with the soul-shifting hypnotism
can make you firmly believe
that you are someone else.
Please take a closer look.
Do you remember now?
Why is it empty?
With the Liluo people's help, Tang Wei
learned the Illusion of Mirrors and Water.
Ten years ago, when you were seriously ill,
he seized the chance to alter your appearance
and applied the soul-shifting hypnotism.
This way,
you were completely convinced
that you were the butler of the Tang Mansion,
Qin Dayuan.
The proof is that
the Divine Constable Bureau
couldn't find Tang Yiming's corpse anywhere.
He's not dead,
so there's no corpse of his.
Tang Wei wanted Tang Yiming to live
and even become another person
to help him take revenge
and kill the accomplices like Huang Gang
and Jiang Zeshui.
But come to think of it.
If we hadn't exposed
the Illusion of Mirrors and Water,
Tang Yiming would have died
believing that he was Qin Dayuan.
In this case,
wouldn't Tang Wei's revenge
come to nothing?
Where did you find this corpse
and the luminous pearl?
There is a secret chamber in Tang Wei's room.
Tang Wei left a will stating that no one
is allowed to enter his room other than
those from the Divine Constable Bureau,
not even Qin Dayuan.
I see.
This way,
even the silliest person would know
that there is a secret hidden in that room.
Turns out that Tang Wei had long planned
for the Divine Constable Bureau to find the body.
Once we find the body,
we'd know that he is fake Qin Dayuan.
There is a secret left in this luminous pearl.
So,
even if we failed to expose
the trick of the Illusion of Mirrors and Water,
we would still be able to learn the truth.
What if I say this item
is related to Liluo?
So,
Mr. Tang left the jade pendant
to me
actually for this purpose.
He knew we would definitely
find the luminous pearl,
and he also knew you would definitely discover
the mechanism of the luminous pearl and the jade pendant.
Tang Wei recorded how he used
the Illusion of Mirrors and Water to alter
Lord Tang's appearance
in the form of images.
The Tang family's mechanisms
are indeed ingenious.
Can't believe
he recorded all the crimes
he committed one by one.
As long as we discover the images stored
in this luminous pearl,
the whole story and the truth
will just come to light.
I taught him the mechanism skills.
This child was really talented.
He was clever
and surpassed his master.
He made this for me to see.
He wanted me
to regret it for the rest of my life.
Lord Tang,
please go back with us.
Although you killed General Hu,
Lord Huang, and Lord Jiang,
your mind was controlled by someone else.
You are also a victim.
You won't receive a heavy sentence.
What is
the point
of living for me?
Lord Tang,
Mr. Tang was scheming,
but
he never forgot the bond you shared
as father and son.
The bond we shared as father and son?
You are wrong.
Wei didn't hate Huang Gang,
Hu Hai,
or Jiang Zeshui.
He hated me.
He hated me for saving him,
raising him,
and making him suffer
in this living hell for 47 years.
You are wrong.
Look.
I will definitely
give you the best of everything.
I will make it up to you
and raise you to be an outstanding man.
This is...
Father, try this.
It's really delicious.
No, thanks.
Just take a bite.
Just one bite.
Alright, I'll take a bite.
[Dignity]
Father!
Wei.
[Dignity]
Wei,
I will be away for a few days.
Don't forget to do your homework.
Don't worry, Father.
Although Tang Wei hated you,
he remembered
every moment
you shared.
That's right.
The Liluo luminous pearl is priceless.
He insisted on making this mechanism
even at the cost of destroying it.
It's enough to prove that your bond
mattered so much to him.
Wei,
you painstakingly
laid out your plans for the past 10 years.
And you left alone,
without even knowing
if your plans would succeed.
Wei,
you were just like how you used to be when you were a child.
I am coming to reunite with you now.
My Lord.
Perhaps living was the real pain
to him, just as he said.
Before he died,
he learned that Tang Wei still cared about him.
I suppose...
he died without regrets.
[God of Hatred, Haiqu]
-Chief. -Chief.
Tang Yiming is dead,
but we still haven't figured out
who the former citizen
of Liluo he mentioned really is.
This case is not solved yet.
Li Si,
you once said that
a middle-aged man with a square face
and narrow eyes
showed up at Lanyue Pavilion.
I asked him before,
and he said he forgot.
How would he confess?
He must be hiding something.
Seems like we still need
to arrest everyone
in the Tang Mansion for strict interrogation.
With so many people at Lanyue Pavilion,
someone must have seen that former citizen of Liluo.
I wonder if you agree, Chief.
So you've been thinking about
that person outside the Tianshu Pavilion
and suspecting me
ever since the Lanyue Pavilion case.
Then,
follow me.
[Tianshu Pavilion]
You're here.
What took you so long?
Master,
I am looking for a middle-aged man
with a square face and narrow eyes.
Too bad
I haven't seen such a person.
The person I'm looking for
once stayed
at Lanyue Pavilion several days ago.
What a coincidence.
I actually went
to Lanyue Pavilion the other day.
It's the Top 1 Pavilion in Great Shi, where you can
go up high and enjoy the view from up there.
And best of all,
it's quiet.
It's much more to my liking
compared to your Star-Gathering Pavilion.
The person I'm looking for
is from Liluo.